<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ivanković family website</title>
    <link>https://www.ivankovic.me/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ivanković family website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 01:01:46 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.ivankovic.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Disclaimer</title>
      <link>https://www.ivankovic.me/disclaimer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 01:01:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ivankovic.me/disclaimer/</guid>
      <description>This is a personal website. Any views or opinions represented in this website are personal and belong solely to the website owner and do not represent those of people, institutions or organizations that the owner may or may not be associated with in professional or personal capacity, unless explicitly stated.
All content provided on this website is for informational purposes only. The owner of this website makes no representations as to the accuracy or completeness of any information on this site or found by following any link on this site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marina Čelar Ivanković</title>
      <link>https://www.ivankovic.me/marina/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 10:49:53 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ivankovic.me/marina/about/</guid>
      <description>I am a Doctor of Veterinary medicine licensed in Croatia and Switzerland.
Currently on career leave to raise a family.
Work history  Volounteer work at the VEF clinics for internal medicine (2012. - 2014.) Volounteer work at the Khulula Wildlife Center, South Africa (2013.) Volounteer work at the county veterinary station in Varaždin (2005.)  Teaching  TA on the Internal Medicine classes (2013. - 2014.) TA on the Comparative Anatomy 101, 102, 103 classes (2009.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marko Ivanković</title>
      <link>https://www.ivankovic.me/marko/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2020 23:25:53 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ivankovic.me/marko/about/</guid>
      <description>I am an Engineering manager and technical lead in the Core Engineering Productivity group. I manage an organization of ~25 engineers, leading multiple teams focused on improving the internal developer experience at Google. I have signifficantly contributed to the following pieces of Googles&amp;rsquo; infrastructure:
 Data Infrastructure Test coverage Mutation testing Large scale code manipulation Large scale code analysis Engineering process metrics Resource usage optimization Machine learning on code and code related artefacts  Work history  Staff Software Engineer / Engineering Manager at Google (2016.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>