<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>automation on Web stranica obitelji Ivanković</title>
    <link>https://www.ivankovic.me/hr/tags/automation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in automation on Web stranica obitelji Ivanković</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Jul 2021 20:46:59 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.ivankovic.me/hr/tags/automation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Smart Home Intro</title>
      <link>https://www.ivankovic.me/hr/marko/blog/2021/smart-home-intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jul 2021 20:46:59 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ivankovic.me/hr/marko/blog/2021/smart-home-intro/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This series of blog posts is my laboratory notebook as I try, and hopefully succeed, in upgrading a 15 year old Central European house into a smart home.
Construction materials The house is 15 years old. It is a well built central european house, with a two-shell external walls made from reinforced concrete and bricks, internal walls made from brick or reinforced concrete and ceilings made exclusively from reinforced concrete.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Čišćenje pretinca elektroničke pošte korištenjem Google Apps Scripta</title>
      <link>https://www.ivankovic.me/hr/marko/blog/2020/simple-newsletter-cleanup-with-google-apps-script/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 14:57:34 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ivankovic.me/hr/marko/blog/2020/simple-newsletter-cleanup-with-google-apps-script/</guid>
      <description>I have recently started to switch more and more of my content consumption to email. Instead of using any social network, like Reddit or Twitter, I subscribe to newsletters directly. This has worked great so far. Every day, I get the hot news from news outlets like BBC, and every few days I get more creative or long form content like XKCD scripts, delivered directly to my inbox.
However, I am not always interested in cosuming the content, and I also don&amp;rsquo;t really want to spend time cleaning up my email when I read something.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
